<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Outdoor Camera &#8211; Camera SA</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/outdoor-camera/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 20:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cam-logo.png</url>
	<title>Outdoor Camera &#8211; Camera SA</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ring Video Doorbell – 1080p HD video, improved motion detection</title>
		<link>/product/ring-video-doorbell-1080p-hd-video-improved-motion-detection/</link>
					<comments>/product/ring-video-doorbell-1080p-hd-video-improved-motion-detection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4455</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[1080p HD video doorbell with enhanced features that let you see, hear, and speak to anyone from your phone, tablet, or PC. An update from the original Ring Video Doorbell, enjoy improved motion detection, privacy zones and audio privacy, and crisper night vision. Receive mobile notifications when anyone presses your doorbell or triggers your built-in &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/product/ring-video-doorbell-1080p-hd-video-improved-motion-detection/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Ring Video Doorbell – 1080p HD video, improved motion detection</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">1080p HD video doorbell with enhanced features that let you see, hear, and speak to anyone from your phone, tablet, or PC.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">An update from the original Ring Video Doorbell, enjoy improved motion detection, privacy zones and audio privacy, and crisper night vision.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Receive mobile notifications when anyone presses your doorbell or triggers your built-in motion sensors.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Powered by the built-in rechargeable battery or connects to existing doorbell wires for constant power.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Easily setup by connecting your Ring Video Doorbell to wifi through the Ring app and mounting with the included tools.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">With a Ring Protect Plan (subscription sold separately), record all your videos, review what you missed for up to 180 days, and share videos and photos.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Pair with select Alexa-enabled devices to enable announcements and two-way talk for convenient in-home monitoring. With a Ring Protect plan (subscription sold separately), Alexa can also make voice announcements and automatically show live video feed on an Echo Show, Fire TV, or Fire Tablet when your Ring doorbell detects a person or package.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/ring-video-doorbell-1080p-hd-video-improved-motion-detection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HIKVISION 8MP Fixed Bullet Camera (DS-2CE16U1T-IT5F)</title>
		<link>/product/hikvision-8mp-fixed-bullet-camera-ds-2ce16u1t-it5f/</link>
					<comments>/product/hikvision-8mp-fixed-bullet-camera-ds-2ce16u1t-it5f/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4433</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fixed Bullet Camera 4K resolution supported up to 80 meters IR distance]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">Fixed Bullet Camera</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">4K resolution supported</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">up to 80 meters IR distance</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/hikvision-8mp-fixed-bullet-camera-ds-2ce16u1t-it5f/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imou Ip Smart Home Camera- Bullet 2C</title>
		<link>/product/imou-ip-smart-home-camera-bullet-2c/</link>
					<comments>/product/imou-ip-smart-home-camera-bullet-2c/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4427</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[*1080P Full HD＆Night Vision: 1080P full HD security camera provides crystal clear videos and recordings even in pitch darkness . Night vision distance up to 30m/98ft. The latest H.265 compression reduces network bandwidth and storage usage by 50% at the same video quality(256g can store about 14 days). Color night vision provides full-color video &#38; &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/product/imou-ip-smart-home-camera-bullet-2c/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Imou Ip Smart Home Camera- Bullet 2C</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">*1080P Full HD＆Night Vision: 1080P full HD security camera provides crystal clear videos and recordings even in pitch darkness . Night vision distance up to 30m/98ft. The latest H.265 compression reduces network bandwidth and storage usage by 50% at the same video quality(256g can store about 14 days). Color night vision provides full-color video &amp; image even in the dark. Night vision distance up to 98ft</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*IP67 WEATHERPROOF: This durable IP67 outdoor camera can withstand temperatures ranging from -22℉ to 140℉ and work in stormy, snowy, and bad weather conditions</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*HUMAN DETECTION &amp; Buil-in Microphone: Powerful image processing technology makes this smart camera accurately identify the moving human body, greatly eliminating false alarms caused by pets, insects and raindrops. And you can customize detection areas and sensitivity. With High quality microphone built into camera can pick up sounds clearly while monitoring</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*Built-in WiFi hotspot : Supports soft AP mode, So you can stream the video, play recording even when there is no Internet connection.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*SAFE &amp; OPTIONAL STORAGE: 100% comply with GDPR Data Protection Regulation to enhance your privacy protection. Only you and your authorized user have access to the images and videos stored on the Micro SD card (maximum 256GB), the Imou Cloud, or a network video recorder</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/imou-ip-smart-home-camera-bullet-2c/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imou Cruiser 4MP WiFi IP Camera 4 MPX, FullColor, IR 30 MT, Siren and White Light, Human Detection,16x Digital Zoom</title>
		<link>/product/imou-cruiser-4mp-wifi-ip-camera-4-mpx-fullcolor-ir-30-mt-siren-and-white-light-human-detection16x-digital-zoom/</link>
					<comments>/product/imou-cruiser-4mp-wifi-ip-camera-4-mpx-fullcolor-ir-30-mt-siren-and-white-light-human-detection16x-digital-zoom/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[*360° COVERAGE &#38; 24/7 FULL COLOR: 4MP QHD glass optics and 2 built-in spotlights provide a crisp and full color images day and night. 355° horizontal and 90° vertical rotation range creates a full coverage. 1 camera installed and 0 detail will be missed *SMART HUMAN MOTION TRACKING: Advanced Artificial Intelligence algorithms distinguishes the moving &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/product/imou-cruiser-4mp-wifi-ip-camera-4-mpx-fullcolor-ir-30-mt-siren-and-white-light-human-detection16x-digital-zoom/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Imou Cruiser 4MP WiFi IP Camera 4 MPX, FullColor, IR 30 MT, Siren and White Light, Human Detection,16x Digital Zoom</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">*360° COVERAGE &amp; 24/7 FULL COLOR: 4MP QHD glass optics and 2 built-in spotlights provide a crisp and full color images day and night. 355° horizontal and 90° vertical rotation range creates a full coverage. 1 camera installed and 0 detail will be missed</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*SMART HUMAN MOTION TRACKING: Advanced Artificial Intelligence algorithms distinguishes the moving human body from other movements so as to filter false alarms. The Wi-Fi camera automatically tracks the motion subject, records real-time videos and sends alerts to your smartphone instantly</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*FLOODLIGHT AND SOUND ALARM: This outdoor camera will be activated the moment human motion is detected. It then automatically turns on the mini flood light, alarms the security siren, records the scene and sends alerts to your smartphone. Stifle any crime in the cradle</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*STRONG WEATHER-RESISTANT: IP66 weatherproof and dustproof design enables the camera to be mounted in any external weather conditions to keep an eye on your home, rain or shine, for this outdoor IP camera withstands temperatures ranging from -30 ° C to 60 ° C. Being equipped with a waterproof plug with a 3-meter power cord, it can be used outdoor hassle-free</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">*SAFER FOR RECORDING: 100% comply with GDPR Data Protection Regulation to enhance your privacy protection. As one of the first manufacturers to have passed the GDPR-derived certification of TÜV Rheinland in respect of data security and privacy protection for IoT products, we adopted advanced TLS encryption technology to protect your privacy. Only you have access to the data stored on the Micro SD card (up to 256GB), NVR or cloud</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/imou-cruiser-4mp-wifi-ip-camera-4-mpx-fullcolor-ir-30-mt-siren-and-white-light-human-detection16x-digital-zoom/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ezviz C8C 1080P Full Hd Wifi Security Camera Outdoor Pan/Tilt/Zoom, 360°</title>
		<link>/product/ezviz-c8c-1080p-full-hd-wifi-security-camera-outdoor-pan-tilt-zoom-360/</link>
					<comments>/product/ezviz-c8c-1080p-full-hd-wifi-security-camera-outdoor-pan-tilt-zoom-360/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4425</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[1080P Pan/Tilt Hd Wifi Surveillance Camera Dome: 352 Horizontal And 95 Vertical Rotation And 1080P Hd Resolution Offer You Good Picture Quality And A Sufficiently Large View. 2.0 Megapixel Cmos Sensor, 4 Mm Focal Length Lens, Maximum Resolution 1920 X 1080. Intelligent Night View Mode: If No Additional Lighting Is Needed, You Can Easily Set &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/product/ezviz-c8c-1080p-full-hd-wifi-security-camera-outdoor-pan-tilt-zoom-360/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Ezviz C8C 1080P Full Hd Wifi Security Camera Outdoor Pan/Tilt/Zoom, 360°</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="featurebullets_feature_div" class="celwidget" data-feature-name="featurebullets" data-csa-c-type="widget" data-csa-c-content-id="featurebullets" data-csa-c-slot-id="featurebullets_feature_div" data-csa-c-asin="B08NDSDLHM" data-csa-c-is-in-initial-active-row="false" data-csa-c-id="n6gph-ejiuj8-1daxlo-j6d1wq" data-cel-widget="featurebullets_feature_div">
<div id="feature-bullets" class="a-section a-spacing-medium a-spacing-top-small">
<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">1080P Pan/Tilt Hd Wifi Surveillance Camera Dome: 352 Horizontal And 95 Vertical Rotation And 1080P Hd Resolution Offer You Good Picture Quality And A Sufficiently Large View. 2.0 Megapixel Cmos Sensor, 4 Mm Focal Length Lens, Maximum Resolution 1920 X 1080.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Intelligent Night View Mode: If No Additional Lighting Is Needed, You Can Easily Set The Camera To The Wi-Fi Mode Night Vision System In Black And White Via The Ezviz App. Thanks To The Intelligent Night Vision Mode, The C8C Automatically Switches From Black And White Monitoring To Colour Monitoring By Turning On The Headlights When It Detects Human Movements.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Flash Alarm: C8C Monitors Important Areas Of Your Home Around The Clock. When Human Movement Is Detected, The C8C Camera Can Automatically Flash Or Manually Set To Flash Both Headlights To Deter Intruders. When The Person Turns Their Head Towards The Flashing Light Source, This Is Clearly Recorded By Our Camera.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Ai &amp; H.265 Personal Detection &#8211; The Built-In Algorithm For Artificial Intelligence Intelligently Detects The Movement Of Human Forms In Real Time And Prevents False Alarms. When People Enter Your Personalised Recognition Area, You Will Be Notified Immediately. C8C Uses The Latest H.265 Video Compression Technology. It Makes The Video Clearer And Smoother While Reducing The Need For Data Storage And Bandwidth.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">Waterproof And Flexible Storage Ip65: With A Full Metal Housing And The Protection Class Ip65, The Camera Can Withstand Rainy, Sunny, Stormy And Even Snowy Days. You Can Save The Recordings As Desired On The Ezviz Cloud Platform Or On An Sd Card Up To 256Gb (Card Not Included).</span></li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/ezviz-c8c-1080p-full-hd-wifi-security-camera-outdoor-pan-tilt-zoom-360/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EZVIZ C8PF WiFi Camera, Outdoor security Camera CCTV with Dual-Lens, 1080p</title>
		<link>/product/ezviz-c8pf-wifi-camera-outdoor-security-camera-cctv-with-dual-lens-1080p/</link>
					<comments>/product/ezviz-c8pf-wifi-camera-outdoor-security-camera-cctv-with-dual-lens-1080p/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[camsa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/camera-sa/?post_type=product&#038;p=4424</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[【Intelligent Dual Lenses】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera stands as the world’s very first smart home camera that achieves 8-time mixed zoom.Users can keep an eye on what’s important without compromising on image quality or clarity. 【Picture-in-Picture Display Mode】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera to provide useful picture-in-picture display, in both live viewing &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/product/ezviz-c8pf-wifi-camera-outdoor-security-camera-cctv-with-dual-lens-1080p/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">EZVIZ C8PF WiFi Camera, Outdoor security Camera CCTV with Dual-Lens, 1080p</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li><span class="a-list-item">【Intelligent Dual Lenses】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera stands as the world’s very first smart home camera that achieves 8-time mixed zoom.Users can keep an eye on what’s important without compromising on image quality or clarity.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">【Picture-in-Picture Display Mode】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera to provide useful picture-in-picture display, in both live viewing and video playback modes through captures a large picture on a small window display, and renders close-up shots on a full screen without blurring the image.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">【AI-Powered Human Shape Detection】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera reduces false or irrelevant alarms by distinguishing human shapes from pets or objects. In addition, you can customize detection sensitivity and time schedules to further filter out unwanted alerts.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">【Mass Storage】EZVIZ C8PF WiFi camera, outdoor security camera has one of the largest on-camera storage capacities in the home security market – up to 512GB, thanks to the built-in card slot. You can enjoy secure local video storage at all times.</span></li>
<li><span class="a-list-item">【Mass Storage】The C8PF has one of the largest on-camera storage capacities in the home security market – up to 512GB, thanks to the built-in card slot. You can enjoy secure local video storage at all times.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/product/ezviz-c8pf-wifi-camera-outdoor-security-camera-cctv-with-dual-lens-1080p/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
